She says I'm crazy
I said I'm not the problem
She says she made me
I said I'm not a product
She says look at us
I just see my reflection
I'm tempted to trust
but she got bad intentions
And she comes at night
She's the devil in disguise
Always picking fights
Trying to take over my mind
She wants my eyes
She's the voice that isn't mine
Nowhere to hide
She's the devil in disguise
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
She's the devil in disguise.
She tries to enslave me, but you can't control the water
She says I am she, but I am God's daughter
Should of known better, 'cause to my recollection
When I have let her, she leads to self-destruction
And she comes at night
She's the devil in disguise.
Always picking fights
Trying to take over my mind
She wants my eyes
She's the voice that isn't mine
Nowhere to hide
She's the devil in disguise.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
She's the devil in disguise
Trying to take over my mind
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
She's the voice that isn't mine
She's the devil in disguise
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
And she comes at night
Always picking fights
She's the devil in disguise
And she wants my eyes
Nowhere to hide
She's the devil in disguise.