Smile when you're sleeping
Wonder who you're dreaming of
Oh, cause I could just see you with wine on your t-shirt
And somebody else on your arm
Can't control this feeling
Wonder who you're dreaming of
After all of these nights laying right by your side
How could my brain make me feel so far?
Maybe it's a case of paranoia
Nervous that I'll never really know ya
What do I feel?
Who do I trust?
Maybe its real,
or maybe I'm just...
Paranoid
Maybe I'm just-
Never felt so naked
Lookin' at you naked
Got your hands down the back of my soul
And the more that I show you, the more I'm afraid
That you're going to wake up
And realize that I'm not the one
That you thought I was
That I thought I was
Am I who I am who am I-
Maybe it's a case of paranoia
Nervous that I'll never really know ya
What do I feel?
Who do I trust?
Maybe its real,
Maybe I'm just...
Paranoid
Maybe I'm just-
Hmm...
I wish I wasn't
Paranoid
Hmm...
Maybe I'm just...