This love has taken its toll on me
She said goodbye too many times before
And her heart is breaking in front of me
I have no choice
'Cause I won't say goodbye anymore
I was so high, I did not recognize
The fire burning in her eyes
The chaos that controlled my mind
Whispered goodbye as she got on a plane
Never to return again
But always in my heart
This love has taken its toll on me
She said goodbye too many times before
And her heart is breaking in front of me
I have no choice
'Cause I won't say goodbye anymore
I tried my best to feed her appetite
Keep her coming every night
Hard to keep her satisfied
Keet playing love like it was just a game
Pretending to feel the same
Turn around and leave again
This love has taken its toll on me
She said goodbye too many times before
And her heart is breaking in front of me
I have no choice
'Cause I won't say goodbye anymore
I'll fix these broken things
Repair your broken wings
And make sure everything's alright
Oh
Oh oh
My pressure on your hips
Sinking my fingertips
Into every inch of you
'Cause I know that's what you want me to do
This love has taken its toll on me
She said goodbye too many times before
And her heart is breaking in front of me
I have no choice
'Cause I won't say goodbye anymore
'Cause I won't say goodbye anymore.