Modern crime prevention task force preparation room
I decline!
I don't think I can be
an effective mentor to that man!
Would you like one?
Oh, sure.
Then, I'll have an amberjack today.
Here you go.
Then, I guess you don't have to be his mentor.
I'm sure he'll act accordingly.
He's an adult after all.
Oh, Kambe!
Your seat's that one.
Um.
Would you like one?
These Gummy Fish are brand new!
A sea bream, a lucky start to the day!
Shut up, Kamei.
It says she died from a drug overdose.
That centerfold model Hoshida Akiko...
Seriously?!
CENTERFOLD MODEL HOSHIDA AKIKO
DIES FROM OVERDOSE
Kato, she was your favorite, wasn't she?
Wait, why are we learning about this
through the media?
Because information
doesn't get passed on to us.
Chief, I'm heading over
to the Stop Shoplifting Campaign now.
Counting on you!
What?
I'll go with you.
I'll be fine by myself.
So don't follow me.
Take me to the scene, Inspector Kato.
Really long to be
When I go all night I need the right to go UNLIMITED
When I go all night I need the right to go unlimited
Isshou teki toukei michibikidasu FACE DOWN
Deducing statistics for a lifetime, face down
Where's I genzaichi juutai no makkana akari ga
Where's I? The deep red light of this traffic congestion
Clicks and clicks turns round and round
Raiders
Raiders, if I ask about my path
Yukute o toeba
Jiki shousouda no way da
It's way too premature, no way
Hey come back, back, back
Chasers yukusue o oeba
Chasers, if I pursue my fate
Tsukareta mayoi kono shinpashii
I'll get tired and lost, this sympathy
Hey you
Hey you!
Pray for the light laying in the dark
Yoru o kakeru ka yoake ni kakeru ka
Will the night run, run to the day?
Drive in the dark going to the light
Utagaeru ka minareta NAVIGATOR
Will I doubt the familiar navigator?
NO LIMIT
No limit
Mugendai kanousei o zero no saki e
The infinite possibility of going beyond zero
NO LIMIT
No limit
Mugendai mitou o susumete NAVIGATOR
Advance through the unexplored infinity, navigator
Mitou o susumete NAVIGATOR
Advance through the unexplored, navigator
Kanousei o zero no saki e
The possibility of going beyond zero
UNLIMITED
Unlimited
Cannot scare UNLIMITED
Cannot scare, unlimited
S
hinjuku
Station
I'm tired.
Click! Hello, this is red panda!
Wait, what the hell?
Hello, this is red panda!
Why the hell did you repeat that?
Two red pandas combine into a raccoon!
That's a whole different animal!
Wait, where are we?
Let's go.
You can go on without me.
Could it be Earth? Finally!
I'm finally communicating with Earth!
These guys are desperate to survive, too.
Hey! I made it back—
Let's go.
It's not about money!
By performing where people can see,
they're improving their skills...
It's a 10k bill!
Let's go drinking!
All right!
Hey! Your money took away
their willingness for labor...
Are you listening?
Mescaline, right?
Interrogation Room A
Who'd you buy from?
THE NEXT DAY
Someone I don't know.
No, you're buying from an acquaintance.
Where did you buy it?
Kabukicho.
That's another lie.
When did you buy it?
About a week ago.
Around what time?
Nine o'clock or thereabouts...
Lately around 9:00 PM,
you've been mostly in Shinjuku.
However, six days ago,
on Wednesday around 8:47 PM,
you got on the subway from Shin-Otsuka
where your home is, and disembarked at Roppongi.
And the next time you got on the train
was the next day, at 10:24 AM.
You bought this in Roppongi.
Who was the dealer?
How much?
What is?
I'll buy information at the price you name.
It'll be worthless unless you speak up
before your partner.
Don't get the wrong idea!
We've been a team together for 10 years!
I'm not going to betray him!
Interrogation Room A
Interrogation Room B
How's it going?
Interrogation Room A
He relies on machines,
then it's about money in the end.
How pathetic.
Getting confessions out
is all about two hearts colliding!
He should totally get lessons from Cho.
I don't care about scum like you.
But when I think about your Momma
who raised you all on her own...
I just can't bear it.
Just spill it all out and start over.
Not for yourself, but for your Momma.
You understand, right?
I-It's Mr. Isezaki. From him...
Isezaki?
It's probably that model Isezaki Yuta.
He graduated from Todai
and does commentary for tabloid shows.
I'll handle the rest.
Yeah.
Well, you're in charge now.
We got the intel.
The guy selling them the drug was—
Some model named Isezaki.
No way! It's already been deposited!
How did you know he lives here?
Everyone should know a Mr. So-and-so.
Excuse me.
Who are you?
Hey there. I'm Mita, from Weekly Bunshu.
Weekly Bunshu
Journalist
Akira Mita
Weekly Bunshu
Journalist
Akira Mita
Weekly Bunshu
Journalist
Akira Mita
Weekly Bunshu
Journalist
Akira Mita
Weekly Bunshu
Journalist
Akira Mita
Weekly Bunshu
Journalist
Akira Mita
He's an entertainment journalist.
Though I'm freelance.
That scoop about Eririn the other day
was all my doing.
Why are you assisting us?
Back when I was with bad company,
Kato seriously scolded me, so...
I can risk my life for Kato!
Come on, don't exaggerate too much.
Tasty.
You've never eaten this before?
No.
There he is!
You live in an impressive place!
It's not that impressive. It's normal.
But we're in the middle of the heart of Tokyo.
Oh. Yui Arasaki.
Well, it's useful for work and stuff.
What?
MISATO, too! Both of them are centerfold
models for Millennium Entertainment!
Are you really living here by yourself?
Are you serious?
I'm definitely going to nab that guy.
Where are you taking us?
That's what they say.
You want to come over?
Jeez, this guy sure has energy!
He's been with about ten girls the past week.
One after another!
I'm so looking forward to the party!
It's another girl
from Millennium Entertainment.
Have I seen that girl before?
That girl with long black hair, right?
Looks like his favorite. Who is that?
Oh, but you like girls
who look more pure and innocent, right?
Kato?
Wh-Wha...
Man. Kato, you're way too innocent.
Shut up.
Okay! Let's go catch them red-handed!
No. Let them stay at large.
What? Why?
If we don't hurry...
The drug that Isezaki sells is over 95% pure.
We're going to leave him at large
to figure out who's behind him.
Hey. How do you know that much?
Hey, Mita.
Huh? Where's Kambe?
Who knows? Rich Boy probably got bored
of playing detective games.
Did you get a lead?
Yeah.
The one behind Isezaki is the Gondawara-gumi.
Looks like the woman with black hair
is one of them, acting as liaison.
I see. No wonder she didn't show up
after hitting up the agencies.
Kato.
How about you go home for now?
You seriously stink.
That woman...
What is this place? A park?
Huh? Damn it.
Come on, give me a break.
What is this building? A hotel?
Y-You...
What are you doing here?
That would be my line.
Is this a restaurant or something?
Members only?
Are you hungry?
Well, that's not what I meant.
Prepare meals for two.
As you wish.
This is a rather pompous joint.
Isezaki is getting the drugs
from Gondawara-gumi.
And, their liaison,
the woman with black hair, entered this place.
What is this place?
Woman with black hair?
Yeah.
She's been together
with Isezaki all the time lately.
A-An armored vehicle?
Why is something like this...
You must be Mr. Kato. A pleasure to meet you.
My name is Kambe Suzue.
Kambe?
Is this your house?!
What's going on with that case?
Isezaki is getting supplied by the major
organized crime group Gondawara-gumi.
Why don't you use this occasion
to crush them all at once?
H-Hold on a minute.
What do you mean, crush?
More like, what the hell are you...
I've been doing undercover work
against Isezaki under Daisuke's orders.
Gondawara-gumi's operations are essentially
controlled by the deputy godfather, Umezu.
Once you apprehend him,
everything would collapse sooner or later.
What's the plan?
There will be a drug party soon,
and Umezu will be attending as well.
Looks like all the centerfold models and
actresses Isezaki rounded up will be attending.
Hoshida Akiko ,
whose case was recent, also will be...
What are you planning to do?
If I have two billion or so, I can arrest Umezu
and destroy Gondawara-gumi.
I couldn't gather enough information
to know about the party. I'll admit that.
But I hate methods that involve
slapping people with wads of money!
You can do as you please.
I'll do things my way.
Mr. Kato!
Um, what about your meal?
And, if you wish, we can prepare a bath.
I'm fine. I'm still working.
He seems quite the serious fellow.
Please have a look at what I've made!
Looks like that party is really going to happen.
I grilled it out from an underling
at Millennium Entertainment.
It's in three days, huh?
Alpha, Bravo, Charlie.
What's this?
Oh. Everyone is referred to
by nicknames at the party.
I think that's the keyword to use
when you enter.
Thank you. Sorry to trouble you.
You're not thinking about going there, are you?
That's dangerous.
If they find you, they'll sink you
under the bay like it's nothing.
I'll pay you back for this sometime.
MANGROVE ENTERTAINMENT, LTD.
ICHIROU KOUCHIYAMA
Hi, I'm Kouchiyama. I'm here as Whiskey!
MANGROVE ENTERTAINMENT, LTD.
ICHIROU KOUCHIYAMA
Please enter.
Please check your belongings here.
Hold onto it for me.
Excuse me.
What about your belongings?
Y-Yeah.
Hey, anyone know where my smartphone is?!
It's the one with Little Wooper on it!
Who the hell took it?
Come on, are you doubting me?!
Wow, how did you know?
Found it!
Mr. Patrol?!
Hey, it's you, right Kambe?!
Get those guys!
Hey! Why would you go upstairs?!
That idiot is in a panic right now.
Kambe!
Wait!
Why would you head up here
to the roof? Damn it!
What the? It's not opening!
Did he lock it?
Are you an idiot? The lock is on this side!
Damn, this won't buy us much time.
Hey, Kambe...
Mita? You...
Man, that was close.
But I did it!
No, besides that...
Open up, damn it! I said open up!
Hey.
I'll say that I threatened you to do all this,
so play along with me!
When will the deposit happen?
Deposit?
Oh, you didn't know?
It can't be...
Kato.
I'm sorry, but I've only got one.
Hey, what the hell is that?
K-Kambe Daisuke!
Purchase of The Tower is now complete.
Balance: Unlimited.
What is this?
Poison gas?!
The hell? What is going on...
Yesterday, the deputy godfather
and effectively the leader
of the organized crime group
Gondawara-gumi Umezu Mikio,
model Yuta Isezaki, and roughly 20 others were
arrested for suspected illegal drug possession.
They said a lot came out
from Umezu's smartphone.
And other crimes, like enough information
about the murder of Hoshida Akiko.
In the case of Suspect Umezu,
once allegations for the murder of centerfold
model Hoshida Akiko have solidified,
he will be rearrested for those charges as well.
Come with me.
I don't like it.
Don't like what?
That someone like you is a cop!
Why did you join the police?
To nab criminals, of course.
But without doing something like
slapping people in the face with a wad of cash.
I heard you used to be
in the First Investigation Division.
However, during a siege incident you misfired,
and the target was seriously injured.
You've been unable to fire a gun ever since,
and moved from First Investigations Division
to Modern Crimes.
You bastard.
Seriously?
It can't be helped!
These are orders from above after all.
Kato!
Yes?
Sorry to ask you this,
but can you head to Hong Kong this weekend?
Huh?!
There's a symposium about international crime,
and we have to send someone over.
I guess I don't mind.
Wow, thank you!
Okay, just ask Kambe for the details!
Sure.
Eh?
Have a nice flight.
Eh?!
EEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEH?!
costs incurred
Items
Price
Total
Bribe to Mita
"The Tower" purchase
$ 770,462,713 USD
Ramen cups orders
Information bought to the comedian
Tip dropped to the comedians
Everybody wanna do what they wanna wanna do
Mukashi dareka ga itta
Someone once said
"anata wa anata wo tsuranuite ikinasai"
"Live what you believe"
Demo tochuu de zettai ironna mon ni
But on the way, you bump into many things for sure,
Butsukari tsuzukete magatte iku
Keep bumping and curving
Ore no hen na magarikata
My weird curve
Omae no hen na magarikata
Your weird curve
Myou ni nanka karamiatte
It tangles up strangely well
Make things a little better
Welcome my friend let's get to work
Welcome my friend, let's get to work
Everybody's here It's time to make some miracles
Everybody's here, It's time to make some miracles
Show must go on
I just need you more than ever
Ore wa aru toki kiita
Once I heard
"wakare wa deau koto yori mo zutto haado da" yeah
"Saying goodbye is much harder than meeting someone", yeah
Douse kekkyoku onaji michi wo aruki tsuzuke
In the end, we keep walking on the same path
Kotoba ni mo dekinai koto to ka kanjou to ka
Things I can't turn into words, emotions and stuff
Wakeatteru uchi ni naze ka wakaranai kedo kitto
By sharing them, for some reason,
Dare yori mo omae no koto wo rikai dekite shimau
I can understand you more than anyone else
Na
Na na
Na na na
Na na na na
Na na na na na
Na na na na na na
Na na na na na na na
Na na na na na na na na
Na na na na na na na na na
Na na na na na na na na na na
Na na na na na na na na na na na
Na na na na na na na na na na na na
Na na na na na na na na na na na na na
Na na na na na na na na na na na na na na
Na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na
Na
Na na
Na na na
Na na na na
Na na na na na
Na na na na na na
Na na na na na na na
Na na na na na na na na
Na na na na na na na na na
Na na na na na na na na na na
Na na na na na na na na na na na
Na na na na na na na na na na na na
Na na na na na na na na na na na na na
Na na na na na na na na na na na na na na
Na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na
Na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na
Na
Na na
Na na na
Na na na na
Na na na na na
Na na na na na na
Na na na na na na na
Na na na na na na na na
Na na na na na na na na na
Na na na na na na na na na na
Na na na na na na na na na na na
Na na na na na na na na na na na na
Na na na na na na na na na na na na na
Na na na na na na na na na na na na na na
Na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na
Na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na
Na
Na na
Na na na
Na na na na
Na na na na na
Na na na na na na
Na na na na na na na
Na na na na na na na na
Na na na na na na na na na
Na na na na na na na na na na
Na na na na na na na na na na na
Na na na na na na na na na na na na
Mata yatte kita
It's here again
Ore dake ja
An impossible scene
fukanou na shiin
Just by me
Omae dake ja
An incomplete piece
fukanzen na piisu
Just by you
Awasatte kamiatte
They get mixed and mesh together
Make things a little better