Dandan me ga mawatte
Bit by bit, my gaze goes dizzy
Yuuyake ga sansan sora ni chitteitta
The setting sun fell into the radiant sky
Shimidasu kumo ni kotoba ga denakunaru no ha naze?
Why is it that words won't form from the dripping clouds?
Toomawari no chikamichi to sutaritateta senro
Via a roundabout shortcut in this route,
waste comes to an end
Shimetta te o tsukanda mama hayaashi de sumu
With your wet hand in mine, we speed forward
Tagai chigai no azemichi ga mizu mitai ni yuraide
The path between the rice fields blurs like water
Semi no ne o bokashita mama tachitsukushita
With the cicada's cries muted, we froze
Natsu ga kinou o tooriokoshiteiku
Summer's come to take the place of yesterday
Kusa no nioi niwaka ame no ondo mazariattara
When the smell of grass and the feel of rainshowers mix
Bokura ga kyou made shiranai hibi ha
There's too many unknown, bygone days to count
Kazoekirenai urokokumo no oku de tashikani yondeiru
Within the cirrocumulus clouds, surely they're calling out
Doro ni mamireta boku no te o kobamu you ni
As if to reject my mud-soaked hand
Muzukashii tte ha nikanda kimi to boku to ja chigau kara
"It's too difficult," you said shyly You and I are different, after all
Dandan me ga mawatte yuugure ga sansan sora ni chitteitta
Bit by bit, my gaze goes dizzy
The setting sun fell into the radiant sky
Omoidasu hodo ni kotoba ga denakunaru nowa naze
Why is it that the more memories return, the fewer words form?
Michitsure ni sansei nara waratte
I laugh when my companions give approval
Tokku ni tooku hanareta kimi ha tada
those I was parted from so long ago, so far away
Mita koto no nai iro ni somatta hitomi de
You just glance with eyes dyed a color no-one's ever seen before
Aa, mabataki no hitotsu mo shinai mama
Ah, without a single twinkle
Otona nanka ni ha wakaranai iro o miteiru
Seeing a color that Grown-ups would never understand