Projection Room
And so...
Shall I show you...
Everyone's true form.
Despite the suspicions, the questions and the answers,
we move towards a quiet place.
Like a tightrope,
we move blindfolded.
To prove this impossible reality,
it is too late to propose and send a mayday notice.
If you noticed, at the door behind that screen,
we have locked ourselves!
This is the judgement in which I still believe
In the dark, we tempt blocks...
That with a loud sound, they collapse.
For whom, or for what
am I here? There is no reason.
What is the truth? I cannot choose.
I stand up while I place my hand on my chest.
This is Not Game, it is not necessary to continue or save.
Although I came to think that I could rewind it,
I will have to confront him for the rest of my life, to try to survive!
Even if everything disappears.
Area of Red Leaf - Maple mountain
That's the end, Onigasaki.
I didn't think you were that dumb.
Speak for yourself, Oshigiri.
I've always wanted to crack that
stubborn head of yours at least once.
And... have you guys decided on what to do?
-I'll go forage for mushrooms.
-Fishing.
Forage for mushrooms!
Fishing!
-Forage for mushrooms!
-Fishing!
You still haven't decided, huh.
Strange odor detected!
Anya farted!
Not me!
You're the culprit, aren't you, Akatsuki!
I... I'm the type that holds it in
in front of others.
I hold it in too!
And Anya, didn't you eat
baked sweet potatoes earlier?
Didn't you eat them too?
And we even split the second one.
You...
We're back, Karirin!
By the way... are Kai and Zakkun
still having a staring match?
It's either mushroom curry or grilled fish.
It's a duel... Onigasaki.
Huh... how so?
I'll go forage for mushrooms in the mountain.
You go fish in the river.
Whoever brings back the best ingredients
and manages to satisfy the others, wins.
Sure, it's on!
The winner gets to
order the loser around for a day.
I expected the same thing...!
I can't win against Onigasaki
with some second-rate mushrooms.
I have to aim for the top... only the king!
Matsutake!
matsutake
I've not really fished in the river much...
But I guess it will work out somehow.
This is an anime, after all.
And so...
Our blazing campfire begins!
Wh... What happened to the both of you?
I fell off a cliff...
I fell down a waterfall...
After all your boasting...
both of you brought nothing back, huh?
Loser
S... Say something...!
Sorry, Makino.
There isn't anything I can give you...
Not even one matsutake mushroom...
Matsutake...
Matsutakeeeeeeee!
It's delicious, isn't it?
Hey, Oshirigi... here.
Matsutake!
Wh... Where did you find it!?
It was growing in the pine forest that I fell into.
Only appears when you aren't looking for it.
Give it to Aikawa to eat.
Oniga... saki...
Actually, I...
Isn't that a sweetfish!
And it's one of those roe-bearing ayu
that's only available this season!
There was a river right by the cliff I fell off.
I was carried by the current for a bit,
and then I happened to grab onto it.
Don't... be mistaken.
I didn't do it for you.
But... you can...
have it anyway.
Dude, you can't just put a raw fish...
straight into a pocket...
What are they on about?
And now...
We shall decide the items
for the 13th Avenue's sports day.
Teacher Paka!
Yes?
I want to take part in the bread eating contest!
You're definitely after the bread, aren't you.
Bread! Bread that looks like Pandarou would be perfect!
And with chocolate cream in it, if possible!
That'd... be tough on the budget...
If it's an alpaca,
there'll be a discount for my face.
Then that's alright. Sorry.
If it's an alpaca,
there'll be a discount for my face.
Then that's alright. Sorry.
Mr. Iride!?
What happened!?
All this ruckus in the morning...
We've switched!
Idiotsuki and I... have switched bodies!
So that means...
Akki and Karirin have switched?
It might be his doing again.
Well, that's not a problem.
This sort of thing happens all the time.
What do you mean, not a problem!
What am I going to do when it comes to changing
clothes and showering and going to the bathroom!?
Well then, I'll try to get more views
on live chat!
Wait!
What are you trying to do!?
Karin, if you're cuter and more bubbly,
the number of views will probably go up too!
Don't mess with my image!
Either way, the both of you have no choice
but to patiently wait to switch back again huh?
So it's Kai who's switched
with Karirin this time huh...
Well.
Then, I'll grab a few views with some paid content!
In your dreams!
Hmph... these are pointlessly huge...
Pointlessly...
I'm going to the bathroom.
Sorry, sorry!
Is everyone alright?
First I must go take a bath!
Getting switched with Yuzu
is the most dangerous!
It's great that there aren't
any problems this time.
Wh... What happened?
Showing off such a
relaxed sleeping face's kinda...
Will I be next!?
What if I become a girl...!?
And if my body gets taken over by a girl...!?
No way...!
That's too frightening, I shan't sleep!
That's right!
I'll be fine as long as I don't sleep!?
If I don't sleep I won't get switched, maybe!
Great!
No no no way! No way!
I mustn't fall asleep!
I said! I shouldn't fall asleep!
If I do...
If... I... fall... asleep...
So Zakkun's been switched this time!?
Oshigiri! Are you alright!?
Yes, but... I haven't gotten switched.
Then, who got switched with Oshigiri?
So for the most part, everything has been decided.
What's left to decide
is the cheerleaders and cheers...
Yup yup!
Karirin and Hiimin will be the cheer girls!
With mini mini skirts and frills!
No... way...
Then let's have a vote... Those voting for?
Yup!
This is clearly unfair.
Mi... Mini skirts are too embarrassing...
And pink frills are even more...
Seems like we've got requests for colors here.
You can go lead the cheer-leading team.
You only take part in one event so far.
Huh, uh...
Won't it be better to have people
whom you want to cheer you on?
What do you mean?
Well... in your case...
Getting cheered on by Aikawa and Iride...
Try your best!
Or getting cheered on
by me, Kudou and Roro,
which would you prefer?
Damn you slowcoach!
Fight~
If you lose, your punishment
will be an hour-long hug!
Ma... Makino...
Area of Hot Spring - SPA center
Feasting your eyes,
Right, Oshigiri?
I... Leave me alone!
By the way, why are there
only swimsuits for the girls?
How about us?
Of course there are swimsuits for you all.
Here they are.
Damn you!
Yup! Yup!
Th... That was just a joke...
Over here.
Watch this!
Hey, what are you doing!
Pacocktail...
It's not here!
Huh? What's not here?
My underwear...
isn't here!
If it's someone among us...
Honestly...
I feel that Yuzu's the most suspicious!
Karirin!?
That's because Yuzu, you often...
...bring home the spoons that this guy has used.
No... No way!
That's not it, Akki!
This time at least, I'm not the culprit!
I have a complete collection
of your underwear already!
Me too, I don't think it's Roromori.
Rather, I think the real culprit...
...is taking advantage of Roromori's
obsession with Iride, don't you think so?
So you're saying that
there's actually someone else who did it?
Yes.
It's Onigasaki.
This guy acts on his own all the time!
Moreover, he's pretty liberal
and has an habit of stealing!
It can't be Oniyaro.
What!?
That's because he usually wears a loincloth.
Why would someone who wears a loincloth
steal Akatsuki's underwear?
Maybe he was after something more Western?
Is that true, loincloth guy?
I like an East-West fusion.
By the way, could you stop calling me by that name?
What's your problem! I was trying to help!
Seems like this has gotten messy...
Isn't he the culprit?
Me!?
Th...that's kind of...
Ms. Inaba!
Yup, that's most likely.
I am innocent!
And I've realized one other possibility!
Another possibility?
Whether or not... Mr. Iride's underwear
was even here in the first place.
that's it!
If the underwear was never even here...!
You mean that Iride was not even wearing
underwear in the first place!
Damn you!
So you go frickin' commando all the time huh!
Nope! What are you all saying?
Iride Akatsuki... you are the culprit!
No no no no no!
Why would I steal my own underwear...
That's because of that.
Masochist.
What's the matter?
Underwear?
(On the sports day)
What's going on!?
Why are you the only one?
Well...
Himiko's not participating because
she's looking after Oshigiri who's got a cold.
Ugh... pink...
Kaikoku escaped in the chaos.
I'll go do some fishing.
Anya and Makino
haven't woken up since morning...
Just 555 minutes more...
Karin and Yuzu are
having an argument about the length
of the skirts for the cheerleaders...
This has to be it!
No way! Not something this short!
And you?
As for me...
My whole body's aching
from the rehearsal two days ago,
"Physical Education 2"
So I'm going to the chiropractor now...
Wow!
Look at this, Anya.
Sakuras are blooming over there!
Don't you want to go admire the flowers?
-Don't you want to go admire the flowers?
-Shut up! You're doing it again!?
Area of Spring - Flower Viewing Park
How beautiful!
This calls for a poem.
The first sakuras,
My heart is joyfully light,
A new life begins.
And then I notice,
The loneliness and setbacks...
Ah...
Stop the poetry.
This is delicious.
This is where Hiimin shows off her talent.
Indeed.
This is a big deal.
Th... Thank you!
This is a clear violation...
Can't believe that sakuras bloom
even in a place like this...
Sakura...
Zakkun why are you so gloomy?
Have some sweet sake!
D... Don't get close!
I told you to stop! Go over there!
Miss, are you feeling alright?
You haven't eaten anything since just now.
Is the food not to your liking?
Ah, that's not it.
I was merely thinking.
Is that so.
Hey!
Are you listening, Onigasaki!!
There should only be
nameko mushrooms in miso soup!
Who made him drink so much...
Zakkun only had a tiny sip, didn't he.
What's more,
he only drank sweet sake for children.
Yuzu, you've changed the way you speak.
You're always ignoring my words of caution!
Have you ever bothered listening to what I think!?
-Hey, Kaikoku, listen up!
-This is bad... He's messed up...
Someone change seats with me...?
Ken...
Ken!
Why did you leave me!?
Who?
That's right! Onigasaki!
Why are you leaving us!?
Don't you feel sorry for us!
Ken!
-Spring is the season of wood ear mushrooms!
-Hey, you idiot, don't get your snot all over me!
The angelic smile of the devil...!
Well, well, Hiimin!
Drink some of this and calm down!
I am INABA.
God of white rice INABA!
White
Rice
No running around during meals.
All living things are babies,
be thankful for your food.
Yes! INABA!
INABA!!
God of white rice INABA!
What should I do... I can't keep up with them.
Karin...
Wh... What!?
You're not like yourself at all, Karin.
What's the usual me like?
Like you're naturally enjoying yourself somehow.
Karirin's drinking too!
Great!
Zakkun! Anbou! Kai! Makimaki!
Shall we all drink another round!
That's why I... Ken...!
God of white rice INABA...
I don't understand this, but INABA!
INABA!
That's great...
I just wish things could go on like this.
I'm not sure about that.
Come on! Anbou!
Cry it all out!
INABA!
Good morning.
Yesterday was fun.
Sorry... I don't remember what happened halfway...
Oshirigiri, maybe you should
just apologize to Kaikoku.
Wh... What did I do to him!?
Jeez... It was a total mess...
Well, this happens all the time...
You've been eating well
since yesterday, Makino...
Truly delicious.
INABA!
INABA...!
God of white rice! INABA!!
Ooh... You all look like you're enjoying yourselves.
Shall we decide on the winner
of the Akapalsy Prize this time?
So who do you think will win the Akapalsy Prize?
Um... sweet sake—
Like a lonely stray cat,
to which nobody pays attention.
On the day I cried in the rain,
you were the one who found me.
You gave me a name, and that name, look,
became a proof that I have acquired
what I want to protect.
I was able to become stronger.
The miracle of meeting you that day,
it gave me the strength
to protect someone.
Now I will separate from you and leave.
Thank you for watching over me.
There is still a lot I want to tell you, but...
... there is still something left in my chest.
I can't talk to you.