Here is the latest traffic report.
At both Misato and Tsukuba junctions,
there has been a truck-related accident.
As such, these junctions are closed for the time being.
Misato's south exit still appears to be currently blocked off-
K a g e r o u   d a z e
Hey, what are you doing?!
Why? How did this happen?
Uhm, we have now seized this department store.
There's no point in resisting.
Jinzou Enemy
Kisaragi attention
Kagerou Days
Mekakushi Code
Yuukei Yesterday
Headphone Actor
Konoha no sekai Jijou
Lost Time Memory
Ayano no koufuku Riron
Kagerou Project - Album song list
The first album is being broadcast on the network!
next, the popular artist...
I feel like directing a movie.
quite a statement for a hikineet to make.
Master, you really want to do something like that?
Yeah, while having a megaphone in hand.
Action!
It hurts!
I'm sorry, I'm so sorry!
I apologise, pardon me! I'm sorry!
What are you doing?
What's wrong with that guy?
Hey, what are you spacing out for?
Do you want to get left behind?
Well, that'd be fine! then I could take Konoha out on a date!
Hold on, Hiyori!
You, what's your problem!?
Huh? Where's that thing I bought earlier?
Ugh, I probably dropped it somewhere!
I'm going to look for it!
Eh? Wait, I'll go look too!
It hurts!
Why did big bro have to show up here, of all places?
That doesn't matter. You shouldn't be wandering off on your own like that.
Kido, let go of my hand...
I'm not a kid, you know...
I'm fine by myself.
No, if I do, then things will get even worse.
What's that supposed to mean?
Well, you know! you're the Mekakushi Dan's mascot!
So you have to be taken care of...
Right, commander?
Yeah..! What she said!
T-that aside, I'm surprised. Was that your older brother?
You two seem pretty different...
Is that so?
We used to get along, despite how we are nowadays.
Emphasis on 'used to'...
This is bad!
Follow me!
Mary!
Master!
Hey!
Did you really see someone with red eyes in that group?
Wait, did I say that out loud?
Um, that's just what I saw... But I may be wrong.
Damn! What could this mean...?
Let's try attacking them! I'm sure the two of us can!
No, it's too dangerous.
Kido and the others aren't here, but they should be nearby.
Our first priority should be finding them...
Mary!?
If everyone's nearby...
...It'll be alright.
Mary!
Hey!
Who are you?! Don't move!
It's dangerous!
Hey, what's wrong?
You...
We managed to defeat these guys... All that's left is...
Kido!
Yeah.
That hurts.
You okay?
Kano, Kisaragi!
Kido!
Take him and Mary with you, and run to the next shop!
What about you?
Seto and I...
What the..
What happened?
This is bad, Mary's power has started to wear off!
Seto!
You brat...!
A hostage is on the run!
Over there! That tall-looking person!
Shit!
Hey! Big bro?
It's no use. He's completely frozen.
Well then...
It'd be best if we stay hidden here for a while.
But they've already identified us as enemies.
They might even start hurting some hostages,
so shouldn't we do something?
Even if you say that... Is your leg alright?
Ah... I can endure it.
What's more, can we even do anything by ourselves?
We're just kids compared to who we're up against.
Luckily, the shutters are closed,
so the enemy can't move around freely.
Even if there were as many people as earlier,
If we don't cause another scene,
then getting attention would be impossible.
However, if you look at this, there seems
to be something on the upper floor-
You had something like this? When did you get it?
I found it earlier.
So the security system on the upper floor
is the center to all of this...
At any rate, simply immobilizing them won't solve all of this.
I'm also curious about the person with
red eyes that this guy mentioned.
Yet we don't have any kind of backup
if something goes wrong.
And whatever we do, we need a way to call for outside help.
Whether or not we get out of here alive depends on it.
According to Kisaragi, this guy's phone
has some kind of amazing hacker.
If we manage to get this guy to that spot on the upper floor,
He could connect it to the system,
and at least open the shutters, right?
I get it!
If we do that, then we'd have the reassurance of the police being here.
Yeah, that makes sense!
...Huh?
That's weird...
His smartphone...
...Isn't here.
It's a smartphone.
Whoa...
It even has earbuds!
I'll have a quick listen...
...I can't hear anything.
Well, I saw that coming.
Even if it was left behind, I can't do anything with it.
I'll just leave it here...
Even if I glare at the sun I found,
TL note: she's singing Yuukei Yesterday.
W-Wow!
Even if I put a lid on this thumping hear-
TL note: she's singing Yuukei Yesterday.
What a weird song.
Alright, It's time to split up, so here's the plan.
While I drag this guy's around,
you two look for his missing phone.
Kisaragi and Mary will be randomly
freezing enemies on this floor.
You and Seto follow them and carry this to the atrium, then install it to the main system.
Huh? that's too heavy-
Seto's injured. He shouldn't force himself.
No- hold on, what about the shutters?
Find a solution by yourself.
Hello, pardon me...
There we go...
This is great!
Will Kido really be ok by herself?
Things are really chaotic right now...
She should be fine. We don't call her
"commander" for nothing.
Even so...
You should worry more about yourself.
You're injured, remember?
I'll take care of installing the display screen,
so you handle tying the frozen terrorists up~
Got it!
Also, make sure to follow those two.
It's gotten quiet, after all.
Isn't it funny to worry about peace and quiet?
Shit, this is heavier than that guy.
I can feel my arms giving out.
Anyways, I can't afford to complain.
As the Mekakushi Dan's leader, that'd be pathetic.
Perfect. Time to do this.
Hey!
Why are you here by yourself!? where's Hiyori?
And why's the shutter closed...?
I have no idea...
What's with all the racket-
Ugh, come on... Something strange
is happening at the shops over there...
For now, I'll look near the bathroom again.
You try searching too, go it?
Oh, also, here's something someone lost.
Make sure to return it!
Hey-
Ow...
Good, with this, nearly all of the enemies should be frozen-
Aww, we have to freeze them all over again...
What was that sound?
Probably that hostage from before.
You wait over there and keep watching.
Understood.
There's no opening...
Why am I always so...
Momo.
Mary?
I'll lure them away, so take that opportunity to run.
Huh? That's too dangerous!
If someone has to be the decoy, I'll-
You can't!
After all, I am your senior!
...shit!
Kisaragi.
Seto.
Are you alright?
Yeah somehow.
Nevermind me, Mary's-
Don't worry, she's fine.
As things are right now, Kisaragi being far from Kido is extremely dangerous.
Can't something be done?
Anything?
For now, just go out there and try to find Kido.
You must be going to join Kido.
But...
Don't worry, I'll find a way to save Mary.
I understand.
There we go...
I can walk by myself now.
So you're finally back to your senses.
S-sorry.
I know you're confused,
but there's no time to explain the whole thing.
No... While I was frozen... I don't know how, but I could see everything that was happening,
so I understand...
That... makes this a lot quicker.
Oh yeah, my phone... I dropped it around here...
Shit.
What to do now?
I wonder if this place's emergency system
could open the shutters.
It seems like it might be accessible without having to connect to other things.
Or maybe there's a way to escape through the vents...?
Maybe if you distract the terrorists for long enough, we could free the hostages without them noticing.
If you find my phone, tell Ene-
Tell that hacker what's going on, please.
If the system the terrorists are using is a broadcast system,
then all we have to do is to find the source.
From there, we should be able to transmit footage freely.
If we find this group's leader, it'll all work out from there.
You really are interesting.
It feels like we've been here recently...
Yeah, we were just here a few minutes ago!
I haven't seen this before, so we must be somewhere new.
How's that supposed to make sense?!
Are you making fun of me?!
Where are your friends hiding?
Hurry up and say it!
Master-
Um... Do you know where Hiyori is?
Who the fuck are you?!
Hey, watch out!
What is this?
That's...
Hey, listen...
I'll help you look for whoever Hiyori is...
But before that, I will need your help.
Hiyori...!
Hold on!
I don't think I could run away fast enough if we attack carelessly.
My injury would hold me back.
What are you doing?!
Guess there's no time to think this through!
Take them to the atrium. My friends are waiting there.
What about you?
Just hurry!
Let's go.
You again?!
How many goddamn times do you gotta get in our way?!
How am I even supposed to find Kido if the terrorists are everywhere?
Oh! I could just use my phone!
It wasn't drowned in tea!
But I don't have the means to fight any terrorists I encounter...
I know!
If I really have the power to attract attention, then...
Please work...!
Hey.
Big bro... And...
Who?
Perfect timing...
Could you lend a hand?
You get it? That makes this easier, then.
Hey, tree people are in the atrium.
Not to mention the shutter next to them is open, somehow...
Hey, what's wrong?!
What happened?!
Hey!
What the hell is that?!
It's like some kind of monster!
Hey, wait!
Nice, Hibiya!
You little...
O-one down!
I did it...
Good job on the aiming.
Doesn't it feel like I'm the only one stuck with the dangerous job?
That's because you're the only one who could do it, Kano.
Sure, that sounds good enough.
You're strolling in here against
an armed opponent empty-handed?
Gotta admit, I'm interested in what kinda insane thought process you have.
Don't you agree, leader?
I think I realized you were a fake
when I was being carried around...
I think he knew for a while now.
Why is this the plan, though?
It's risky to have him all alone, right?
I don't know why, but you needed to hide yourself.
Well, Shintaro said there was someone
with red eyes in that group.
So it was best to install the display monitors while hiding our intentions
of finding who that person was, and what power they might have.
Yeah, if it was a power like mine,
we'd be in real trouble.
Thank goodness it turned out to just be our imaginations.
Even if some kind of ambush were to happen,
you thought you'd be fine by hiding right here.
What are you talking about?
"To deceive your enemies,
you must first deceive your friends", right?
You and I both know I can't refuse when it comes to deceiving!
Didn't you hear me?
I said an ambush's gonna happen!
I'm counting on you, Ene!
I'll be done in the blink of an eye!
slow motion
photo
square
slow motion
photo
square
slow motion
video
photo
square
slow motion
video
photo
square
Action!
slow motion
video
photo
square
Hey there! It's me, Kisaragi Momo!
Today, I'd like to introduce you to someone!
Wow, amazing!
She's good at showing up, isn't she?
Hey, you bastards!
Give it up already!
Here is the Mekakushi Dan's...
mascot!
-Woah, you unexpectedly were at ease back then.
-I was scared!
Eh? Was it just a stupid thing to do?
Haha, this is how we are.
Was there no red-eyed person in that terrorist group...?
Not to mention these guys... look pretty used to this.
Master!
C'mon, you're walking too slow!
You're gonna get left behind!
Yeah...
Bit by bit, my gaze goes dizzy
dandan me ga mawatte
The setting sun fell into the radiant sky
yuuyake ga sansan sora ni chitteitta
Why is it that words won't form from the dripping clouds?
shimidasu kumo ni kotoba ga denakunaru no ha naze?
Via a roundabout shortcut in this route, waste comes to an end
toomawari no chikamichi to sutaritateta senro
With your wet hand in mine, we speed forward
shimetta te o tsukanda mama hayaashi de sumu
The path between the rice fields blurs like water
tagai chigai no azemichi ga mizu mitai ni yuraide
With the cicada's cries muted, we froze
semi no ne o bokashita mama tachitsukushita
Summer's come to take the place of yesterday
natsu ga kinou o tooriokoshiteiku
When the smell of grass and the feel of rainshowers mix
kusa no nioi niwaka ame no ondo mazariattara
There's too many unknown, bygone days to count
bokura ga kyou made shiranai hibi ha
Within the cirrocumulus clouds, surely they're calling out
kazoekirenai urokokumo no oku de tashikani yondeiru
As if to reject my mud-soaked hand
doro ni mamireta boku no te o kobamu you ni
"It's too difficult," you said shyly you and I are different, after all
muzukashii tte ha nikanda kimi to boku to ja chigau kara
Bit by bit, my gaze goes dizzy, the setting sun fell into the radiant sky
dandan me ga mawatte yuugure ga sansan sora ni chitteitta
Why is it that the more memories return, the fewer words form?
omoidasu hodo ni kotoba ga denakunaru nowa naze
I laugh when my companions give approval
michitsure ni sansei nara waratte
those I was parted from so long ago, so far away
tokku ni tooku hanareta kimi ha tada
You just glance with eyes dyed a color no-one's ever seen before
mita koto no nai iro ni somatta hitomi de
Ah, without a single twinkle
aa, mabataki no hitotsu mo shinai mama
Seeing a color that grown-ups would never understand
otona nanka ni ha wakaranai iro o miteiru