I had a father, and I had a mother.
I believe I had a happy childhood.
However, ever since a certain day,
everything had changed.
Meeting room 2
Hoshino, did something happen?
No, not really.
Meeting room 2
The days after that were all hollow,
and everything was so boring.
Hey everyone.
Whoops.
Sheesh. This damn website with their ads.
The guys in First Division are in a flurry.
You heard anything?
I don't know anything in particular.
UNSOLVED CASE FILES
1998 ①
Hello, Modern Crimes Force.
It was in Japan.
Yes. Understood.
Chief, the Security Department
says they're short on manpower,
so they'd like a couple of us
as backup for the Classic Car Festival in Ginza.
Okay, I'm trusting you with it.
I'll go, and then one more person...
Always so sudden, talking as they please...
We ain't that bored.
Kamei.
Oh no, I just found a website
I can't overlook and—
I heard that Motoyama from Security
has been deployed as well.
Sacchan is?!
Let's go, Kato!
Saeki
Kato
Kamei
Out - Returning 9pm
Out - Heading straight home
Well, we'll be back around 9pm.
Modern crime prevention task force preparations room
My name is...
...Kambe Daisuke .
Really long to be
When I go all night I need the right to go UNLIMITED
When I go all night I need the right to go unlimited
Isshou teki toukei michibikidasu FACE DOWN
Deducing statistics for a lifetime, face down
Where's I genzaichi juutai no makkana akari ga
Where's I? The deep red light of this traffic congestion
Clicks and clicks turns round and round
Raiders
Raiders, if I ask about my path
Yukute o toeba
Jiki shousouda no way da
It's way too premature, no way
Hey come back, back, back
Chasers yukusue o oeba
Chasers, if I pursue my fate
Tsukareta mayoi kono shinpashii
I'll get tired and lost, this sympathy
Hey you
Hey you!
Pray for the light laying in the dark
Yoru o kakeru ka yoake ni kakeru ka
Will the night run, run to the day?
Drive in the dark going to the light
Utagaeru ka minareta NAVIGATOR
Will I doubt the familiar navigator?
NO LIMIT
No limit
Mugendai kanousei o zero no saki e
The infinite possibility of going beyond zero
NO LIMIT
No limit
Mugendai mitou o susumete NAVIGATOR
Advance through the unexplored infinity, navigator
Mitou o susumete NAVIGATOR
Advance through the unexplored, navigator
Kanousei o zero no saki e
The possibility of going beyond zero
UNLIMITED
Unlimited
Cannot scare UNLIMITED
Cannot scare, unlimited
I heard the First Investigation Division guys
drink at a pretty nice place in this area.
Oh, that reminds me,
you used to be in First Division—
Sorry.
What's that? Looks amazing.
It's not a car that someone
with a respectable job would ride.
This place would be fine, wouldn't it?
No, then that place we saw earlier
was better than this one.
You think so?
This place looks pretty good though.
Metropolitan Police Department
Quite the scene we've got here.
BUS STOP
Apparently the prince of Abura Emirates
will be participating.
I heard he's a speed demon, scooping up cars
left and right with his oil money.
Anyway, aren't there too many?
Where is Motoyama?
Lost Child Guidance
Man, we're getting worked to the bone with
cheap pay, and they get to ride cars like this.
Money isn't everything.
We're doing this for justice.
You're so stubborn.
Isn't that the reason why they
booted you from First Division?
What was that?
Huh?
Those were First Division guys.
What about here?
That guy. I'm sure that guy knows some judo.
Look at his potsticker ears.
But we have this, too.
Don't underestimate judo!
Those chokeholds are nothing to laugh at!
They'd take you down in an instant!
Are you sure you're serious about this?
O-Of course I am!
This isn't good. I have no idea.
It's 35 more minutes until 12 o'clock.
Hoshino!
You got a case?
It has nothing to do with you.
What do you mean?
We're saying this is a case for First Division
and you're not authorized personnel.
Lost child guidance
Go look for some lost kids.
W-Wait, Senpai!
A man suspected of being the bomber
targeting the prince has been located.
Target is fleeing, currently in
Ginza District 1, heading towards Tokyo Station.
I repeat, a man suspected of being the bomber
targeting the prince has been located.
What the hell is going on?
I said, this has nothing to do with you anymore!
Suspect under custody!
I repeat, suspect under custody!
What about here?
The security guard looks like an old man.
No way. Veteran guards are the worst.
If he can do the job as a security guard,
that means he has a lot of experience.
If we can find somewhere
with a frail-looking girl as the guard...
I've had enough. I'm going home.
Wait, Yoko!
Come on, let go of me!
Are you going to abandon me?
Huh?!
In the first place, you're the one
who used up all the syndicate's money!
And you spent that money on other women!
I'm begging you, Yoko.
They're going to sink me down.
If you abandon me now...
That place looks good!
Looks like they got money,
and no security guards in sight!
If there was advance warning of a crime,
why didn't you make them cancel the event?
Of course we suggested they cancel.
But there was interference from the Kantei.
They insisted the prince, who'll be
the next king, come to Japan at this time.
That's a completely different matter.
Human lives are at stake!
You haven't changed a bit.
You don't need to brandish such naïve justice
now that they've
kicked you out of First Division.
As long as the police is a public office,
we have to be on good terms with the government.
Office of superintendent General
Are you sure?
If you wish so, I can get you in
First or Second Investigation Division.
No, I would like the division that I requested.
I see.
No, I'm fine.
It's me.
Oh really, you arrested him?!
And what about the bomb?
Hands up!
Hurry up and raise 'em!
Put all the money and jewelry
you've got in here!
Huh?
Yoko, we don't really need the jewelry.
Might as well while we're at it.
Hurry up!
We have no jewelry.
You mocking me, you little prick?
There's a ton of...
They're chocolates.
These aren't sweet.
Those are made of 75% cacao,
and what we're famous for.
Delicious!
The explosives seem to still be in the car
that the suspect had been using.
The car is a white van, with
Fukunishi Cleaning written on the sides.
I repeat, the explosives seem to still be in
the car that the suspect had been using.
The car is a white van, with
Fukunishi Cleaning written on the sides.
That's it!
Sacchan!
Are you all right?
Yes.
I'm glad.
Hey! What the hell are you—
Shut up!!
Hurry, let's go!
Uh, let's see...
This one has its key in it!
Kamei!
Sacchan. I always thought of you as...
Kamei?
Kamei...
Hurry up and get on your feet.
A paint bullet.
Ow!
Twenty-five more minutes.
What the...
What the hell is that?
Maybe it's the prince...
Damn it!
Stop!
Hey, you!
What the hell are you thinking?
You're under arrest for obstruction of police—
Kambe Daisuke.
As of today, I have been appointed as inspector
of the Metropolitan Police Detective Division.
How was it?
There's only 80k in here.
I didn't think it was a chocolate shop.
Want some?
No.
Let's turn ourselves in.
There's no way we can outrun them-
Wh-What the hell is going on?
Inspector, you say?
Hey! Give me more details on...
AC Cobra... Already tuned up...
Get off. This car will be purchased
by the Metropolitan Police.
What is that guy saying?
The police is asking you to sell this car.
I'll sell it for 300 million.
Tell that to this poor-looking cop...
Wh-What the...
This is the seventh prince of the
Abura Emirates!
Mind your manners!
H-Hey! Call the police!
You're looking at him.
HEUSC, my checks.
As you wish.
I transferred a billion yen.
Keep the change.
Deposit complete. Balance: Unlimited.
Hey! Wait!
Watch where you're going, you youngin!
What the hell is going on?
I don't care! Just stop!
Let's hurry up and turn ourselves...
Let's go as far as we can.
Hey! You're going after the perp, right?
HEUSC, current location of the car in question?
Huh?!
Fleeing from Shimbashi in Minato Ward
towards Shinagawa.
Lead them towards Kachidoki Bridge.
Get rid of all police cars, too.
Understood.
What the? What's the meaning of this?
You're making quite the show here.
How are you going to
take responsibility for this?
HEUSC, identify all individuals, vehicles,
and buildings involved in this commotion.
Send reimbursements
for double the damage costs.
Understood.
Who have you been talking to?
My butler.
Ten more minutes.
Damn it, over here too.
Hey! Chuo Street's got a traffic jam, too!
Do some proper navigation!
Lost 101 Ginza store
Medical tower
Ginza 888
Tatsuya
Iwata Building
Four sutra newspapers
Old meeting hall bridge
Silver hot spring
District 24
Fifth life temple
Hanami Street
Plaza FK
There's a localized traffic signal failure
from Ginza to around Shimbashi.
The current traffic jam
is extending towards Kyobashi.
All emergency vehicles within the affected
area are requested to take detours.
What the hell is going on?
The cop cars are gone.
More like, why are there so few cars?
I really don't get what's going on here.
What's going on?
More like, what happened
to all the other police cars?
The target vehicle
will arrive at Kachidoki Bridge shortly.
We won't make it.
We have to evacuate the residents in the area.
Yoko. I'm really sorry
I got you roped into something like this.
All things considered, something isn't right.
You're right. Robbing a jewelry shop
in Ginza was such a silly...
Back up. Back up!
It's going to blow! What the hell are you doing?
Isn't it obvious?
I'm dropping it into the river.
Tokyo movable bridge opening special request form
Damn it!
Y-Yoko, I'm sorry!
You're kidding!
You're kidding me, right, Hiroshi?
No way! Wait!
This is bad! Not good, no, no, no, no!
Damn it!
Hiroshi, you idiot! I'll kill you!
Remember that!
Who are you?
Move!
Hurry up and jump out!
Yoko... Are you all right?
Y-Yoko!
Give me a break!
I'm so glad you're okay, Yoko!
I can't do anything without you.
Hiroshi.
THE NEXT DAY
Good morning, Chief.
The incident report...
Looks like they're okay without one.
Did you hear?
Of what?
The damages for this case.
Apparently double the market price was paid.
I'm so glad you came!
This is Kambe Daisuke.
He will join our ranks as of today.
He's from the famous Kambe family,
and went through special training in England.
Th-That guy...
Hey.
What the hell was that?
What?
That's not the way a cop handles things.
You're no superhero.
Infinite lives would not be enough.
I see.
So, how much?
costs incurred
Items
Price
Total
Prince's car purchase
Car chase's damage costs (x2)
Traffic light hack
$ 12,748,728 USD
Utility poles destroyed
Daisuke's car repairs
Rear-view mirrors destroyed
Bastard!
Everybody wanna do what they wanna wanna do
Mukashi dareka ga itta
Someone once said
"anata wa anata wo tsuranuite ikinasai"
"Live what you believe"
Demo tochuu de zettai ironna mon ni
But on the way, you bump into many things for sure,
Butsukari tsuzukete magatte iku
Keep bumping and curving
Ore no hen na magarikata
My weird curve
Omae no hen na magarikata
Your weird curve
Myou ni nanka karamiatte
It tangles up strangely well
Make things a little better
Welcome my friend let's get to work
Welcome my friend, let's get to work
Everybody's here It's time to make some miracles
Everybody's here, It's time to make some miracles
Show must go on
I just need you more than ever
Ore wa aru toki kiita
Once I heard
"wakare wa deau koto yori mo zutto haado da" yeah
"Saying goodbye is much harder than meeting someone", yeah
Douse kekkyoku onaji michi wo aruki tsuzuke
In the end, we keep walking on the same path
Kotoba ni mo dekinai koto to ka kanjou to ka
Things I can't turn into words, emotions and stuff
Wakeatteru uchi ni naze ka wakaranai kedo kitto
By sharing them, for some reason,
Dare yori mo omae no koto wo rikai dekite shimau
I can understand you more than anyone else
Na
Na na
Na na na
Na na na na
Na na na na na
Na na na na na na
Na na na na na na na
Na na na na na na na na
Na na na na na na na na na
Na na na na na na na na na na
Na na na na na na na na na na na
Na na na na na na na na na na na na
Na na na na na na na na na na na na na
Na na na na na na na na na na na na na na
Na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na
Na
Na na
Na na na
Na na na na
Na na na na na
Na na na na na na
Na na na na na na na
Na na na na na na na na
Na na na na na na na na na
Na na na na na na na na na na
Na na na na na na na na na na na
Na na na na na na na na na na na na
Na na na na na na na na na na na na na
Na na na na na na na na na na na na na na
Na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na
Na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na
Na
Na na
Na na na
Na na na na
Na na na na na
Na na na na na na
Na na na na na na na
Na na na na na na na na
Na na na na na na na na na
Na na na na na na na na na na
Na na na na na na na na na na na
Na na na na na na na na na na na na
Na na na na na na na na na na na na na
Na na na na na na na na na na na na na na
Na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na
Na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na
Na
Na na
Na na na
Na na na na
Na na na na na
Na na na na na na
Na na na na na na na
Na na na na na na na na
Na na na na na na na na na
Na na na na na na na na na na
Na na na na na na na na na na na
Na na na na na na na na na na na na
Mata yatte kita
It's here again
Ore dake ja
An impossible scene
fukanou na shiin
Just by me
Omae dake ja
An incomplete piece
fukanzen na piisu
Just by you
Awasatte kamiatte
They get mixed and mesh together
Make things a little better